question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The retail disc of Tony Hawks Pro Skater 5 only comes with the tutorial.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In The Sims series, the most members in a household you can have is 8.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "Unturned originally started as a Roblox game.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In the game Melty Blood Actress Again Current Code, you can enter Blood Heat mode in "
                 "Half Moon style.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The first Metal Gear game was released for the PlayStation 1.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The names of Roxas's Key blades in Kingdom Hearts are Oathkeeper and "
                 "Oblivion.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "All of these maps were in Tom Clancy's Rainbow Six Siege on its initial release: House, Clubhouse, "
                 "Border, Consulate.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The video game Fuel has an open world that is 5,560 square miles?",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "The Paradox Interactive game Stellaris was released in 2016.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
     "question": "In The Witcher 3, the Zoltan Chivay Gwent card can be found under the Hanged Mans Tree.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
